<AKHILESH KUMAR>

544 B/ 117 Kanhai Khera, Campbell Road, Lucknow 226003

akhileshkr236@gmail.com (+91) 7905818825

Front End web Developer with 2+ years of experience in building web applications. Eager to join your company to develop out-of-the-box user interface for applications. Skilled in developing plans, managing projects, and most importantly understanding the user's requirements.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

UI Developer

MetaDesign Solutions
June 2021 - Present

Collaborate with product managers and designers to iterate on requirements, designs, and implementations.

Bridge the gap between user interface design and technical implementation.

Currently working on Responsive design, JS libraries(Angular) for enhanced interactions.

Jr. Front End Web Developer

Vorrow Techonology pvt. ltd. Oct 2020 - May 2021

Reviewing code, writing documentation and following test procedures.

Handling the production of software components, which includes UI design, graphics development and programming

Freelancing

As a freelancer Jun 2019 - Sept 2021

Took projects and completed few websites for few personal clients (Team of 4).

EDUCATION

Master of Business Administration

IMS Lucknow 2019 Major in Finance and Marketing

Bachelor of Technology

JK Institute of Applied Physics and Technology, Allahabad 2017

Major in Electronics and Communication Engineering

SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES

- HTML, CSS, javaScript/jQuery, mySql, Angular, Bootstrap,
- Teamwork, multitasking, and attention to details
- Software and web development
- Softwares: Adobe Photoshop,
 Illustrator, After Effects, XD/Figma,

LANGUAGES

- Hindi(Native)
- English

</UI DEVELOPER>